

WERSITE: EMAIL: PHONE:

SAMSONKLITSNER.COM SKLITSNER@GMAIL.COM 415.513.2502

I am an artist and designer currently living in Los Angeles, California. I graduated from UCLA in 2016 with a BA in Design | Media Arts where I focused on building interactive media experiences in the form of performance, software and sound installations.

Education BA Design | Media Arts

University of California, Los Angeles

2013 - 2016

Skills Code Experience

Javascript, React, G-Spea Jquery, Python, C++, Processing, Arduino, HTML/CSS

Software

Git/Github, Ableton (sound design), Max/ MSP, Unity, Adobe Suite, Sketch, Maya,

Exhibitions,

2016 Exhibited work at Play16 (Hamburg, Germany)

**Awards** 2016 UCLA Arts 1st Senior Scholarship

2016 DMA Curator Award

2015 Exhibited work at Photographer's Gallery (London)

2015 UCLA Arts 1st Senior Scholarship

References

Pete Hawkes

Director of Solutions and Design

Pete@oblong.com 801.362.3133

Justin Manor

Sosolimited Founder justin@sosolimited.com

619.241.2998

Victoria Vesna

ArtSci Founder + Director

vesna@arts.ucla.edu 310.709.7257

Casey Reas

Processing Founder, Artist, UCLA Professor

reas@ucla.edu

Experience

Interaction Designer **Oblong Industries** 

Dec 2016

- Jan 2019

R&D, prototyping and building out custom solutions for clients like IBM, Mckinsey, BMW UI design and front end development with tools such as Arduino, G-speak, Javascript, Processing for multi-display spatial environments.

**Creative Technologist** UCLA ArtSci Center

around Brainwave Research.

Aug 2016 - Dec 2016

Programmed networked Arduinos and Max/MSP patches for an EEG sensor project developed

Design Intern Sosolimited

June 2015 - Sep 2015

Front end web development, design protoyping and documentation for small interactive design studio located in Boston

**Head Curator** DMA UG Exhibition 2016

2015

Directed a team of students organizing and curating UCLA's annual undergraduate Design Media | Arts exhibition.

Student Researcher Code the Sound, Move The Noise

Created tutorials and examples for the Processing Sound Library under direction of Casey Reas and

Wilm Thoben.